Stand down, PX-1.
It's him. It's the real Kuma.
I see you survived, Ro-Ro-Noah.
Hey, Zoro!
Come on, let's get out of here while we can.
Is he... gone?
No.
What happened? Where is he?
Zoro! He just disappeared!
Eliminated friends! The final day of the Straw Hat crew!
Zoro!
He's gone!
What the hell did you do to him?!
You! Where is he?!
Where is he?!
You bring him back here, you monster!
Zoro...
What did you do?!
No!
Zoro!
Chopper! Stop this!
You've lost control!
Warrope!
Where the hell are you?
This beast has gone mad, but that's not what worries me.
I want to know what he's doing here.
Well, Bartholomew Kuma.
Can't trust pirates.
The Seven Warlords are supposed to be at Navy HQ.
I wish I could help, but there's nothing I can do.
It's like Zoro was erased.
I'm going to guess that means this guy's the real Kuma.
There's no question.
That power he used, I've seen it before.
Back on Thriller Bark, he erased a girl like that.
Just made her disappear.
And that was the last I saw of her.
Let's just hope he's still alive.
Hey!
What the hell did that guy do to Zoro?
Where is he?
You think I'm going to answer you?
Did you forget I'm the world's most guarded man?
But someone might tell you he can send you flying for three days and nights with those paw pads.
Can't say if it's true or not, but that's the rumor.
Only Kuma knows where they go.
But there's no way you're going to find your friend on these islands.
Or anywhere else around here, for that matter.
He'll probably land on the other side of the world.
What?
Say something, dammit!
Tell us what you did!
Tell us where you sent Zoro!
So that's the real deal, huh?
The first three were bad enough.
And now he shows up to finish the job.
There's no way to win.
What kind of power is that?
Stop it!
Get back!
No!
Stay away from me!
I've got 8,000 men under my command!
Don't make me unleash them on you!
Usopp, he's behind you!
Get down!
Oh, crap!
Usopp, no!
Don't interfere.
He erased him?
But why?
That was PX-1 he just hit!
What's your problem, you fool?
That was your ally!
Just run!
Move, you guys!
Just go!
Get out of there!
We can figure out a plan once we're safe!
Run!
All right, you heard him!
But, Zoro...
The captain just said we can figure it out after we're safe!
Come on!
Come on, buddy!
That last beam just grazed me!
I can help you walk!
Go, you two!
I'll cover you!
Stop it, Brooke!
That's crazy!
I'll protect you!
Even if it costs me my life!
Oh, but I'm already dead, I suppose...
Brooke, no!
That bastard did it again!
Damn it!
How the hell can I let this happen?
The bastard's erasing all my friends right in front of me!
Get the...
Sanji!
Start running, Usopp!
Not a chance!
I'm not going without you, Sanji!
Son of a bitch!
Sanji!
Just run!
Come on!
Nobody does that to my crewmate!
Sanji!
No!
Get back!
Stay away!
Stop where you are!
Get back!
Blavestar!
One more!
God!
Go away, please!
Just leave me alone!
They're alone!
Usopp, run!
Stop it!
Usopp!
Suji!
Damn you!
You can't win! Don't fight!
He got Sanji. What now? What do we do?
It can't be. They're all gone.
It's starting to sound like they could really use my help over there.
There's only so much an old man can do.
I guess I'm not quite the fighter I used to be.
So, fending off a Navy Admiral isn't enough to make you satisfied, huh?
Why don't you keep those thoughts to yourself?
You're already making me look bad, you know?
Oh!
Dark King Rayleigh, correct?
Promo?
Wait, Luffy!
you can't be serious you're asking me to trust you that's entirely your decision
but i'm putting my own neck on the line too all right i feel like i deserve an explanation here
coma this matter is of no consequence to the government so i have no obligation
to cooperate with the navy and you deserve nothing of the sort you bastard
now second gear let's move it
get the hell out of our way
what the
luffy
no
someone help me
oh
luffy
top of no
oh
No!
Chopper, no! Don't do it!
Damn it!
No more. Please stop. Please stop. Just stop.
Please stop.
Stop it! Leave her alone!
Floofy!
Robin!
Whoa?
How could I?
I'm useless!
I got a question.
You ready?
Will you join our crew?
I've never been this happy in my life.
Come on, Straw Hat.
You can't hide from me.
Well, come on.
Get on my ship.
Captain's orders.
What can I say?
You don't leave me much choice.
I got to take care of my masterpiece after all.
So set sail.
I'm joining the crew.
Why did you come to save me in the first place?
Do you hear me?
I just want to die.
There's still something I want to hear you say.
Tell me you want to live.
I want to live.
Shut up.
Even if I don't have friends, I can still buy for something I believe in.
You're wrong.
You do have friends.
I'm your friend, reindeer.
Me!
I'm going to stay here for now.
But if you wanted to, you could stop by here again.
Shut up!
Let's go!
What do you want?
You don't know anything about this.
This has nothing to do with you.
I told you to leave this place.
Luffy.
Help me.
You'll always be my friend!
Wait.
Your dream is foolish.
Then again, so's mine.
Huh?
You hear me?
I want to be the cook on your ship.
Thanks, you geezer.
I owe my life to you, old man.
What are you talking about?
Get on already.
Huh?
We're friends, right?
So get on.
Come, come!
Pull it!
You idiot.
You knew it would end like this.
You knew you could never beat me!
I'll do anything!
Please let me join the crew!
Just one more time!
Hurry up!
Grab on already!
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame.
I will never!
Never be defeated again!
Is that okay?
King of the pirates!
Zoro.
Usopp.
Sanji.
Nami.
Chopper.
Robin.
Frankie.
Brooke.
They're...
They're all gone.
I couldn't save any of them.
What's wrong with me?
So, you're just gonna blast him off like the rest?
You can't pull this mess without an explanation, you know.
And boy, it had better be a good one.
You and I, we'll never meet again.
Farewell, Stryad.
Grove 12, the Sabaody Archipelago, deep in the Grand Line.
On this day, the Straw Hat Pirates, led by Captain Monkey D. Luffy, came face to face with true despair.
And one by one, they were eliminated.
That was harsh.
I think I could use a break from serious stuff.
Lucky for you, we've got a Boss Boothy episode up next.
Everyone's taking to the streets for a portable shrine race.
I hear first prize is a sacred treasure.
Mmm, sacred treasure.
Sounds yummy.
It's not food.
On the next One Piece, feudal era side story, Boss Luffy appears again.
I'm gonna be a policeman.